{
    "subject": "resource/Federica_Mogherini",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Rome",
    "human_readable": "Federica Mogherini was born in Rome.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8802450895309448,
            "question": "Where was Federica Mogherini born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6514908671379089,
            "question": "What is Federica Mogherini's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5430333614349365,
            "question": "What is Federica Mogherini known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37336406111717224,
            "question": "Name a significant policy area that Federica Mogherini has been involved in."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3266277611255646,
            "question": "In what Italian city did Federica Mogherini spend her early years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22881866991519928,
            "question": "Can you describe Federica Mogherini's political affiliations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22733919322490692,
            "question": "Has Federica Mogherini held any other notable political roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.225759819149971,
            "question": "During which period was Federica Mogherini the High Representative of the Union for Foreign Affairs and Security Policy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22191065549850464,
            "question": "What is one of Federica Mogherini's key accomplishments in her political career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1995624452829361,
            "question": "What political positions has Federica Mogherini held?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Federica Mogherini was born in Rome.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6231_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is one of Federica Mogherini's key accomplishments in her political career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6231_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=During which period was Federica Mogherini the High Representative of the Union for Foreign Affairs and Security Policy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6231_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Federica Mogherini held any other notable political roles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6231_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6231_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6231_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6231_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6231_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6231_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6231_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6231_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6231_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6231_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6231_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the format you requested:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Federica Mogherini was born in Rome, as indicated by various sources such as her birth name, place of birth, and date of birth."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents consistently state that Federica Mogherini was born in Rome, Italy. Therefore, the statement \"Federica Mogherini was born in Rome\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}